=Afterlife of Love and Revenge= =Episode 14=
= الآخرة من الحب والانتقام = = الحلقة 14 =
You're so busy.
أنت مشغول جدا.
Now, Pei Medicine Store has closed.
الآن ، تم إغلاق متجر باي للأدوية.
Our medicine store has reopened.
أعيد فتح متجر الأدوية الخاص بنا.
Tell me honestly. How much have you earned?
قل لي بصراحة.  كم كسبت؟
After buying over Pei Medicine Store,
بعد الشراء من متجر باي للأدوية ،
we've used all the money we earned.
لقد استخدمنا كل الأموال التي كسبناها.
Stop telling me that you're poor.
توقف عن إخباري أنك فقير.
All the chores
كل الأعمال الروتينية
were done by me.
تم من قبلي.
How can you not share some money with me?
كيف لا يمكنك تقاسم بعض المال معي؟
You want to have a share?
تريد أن يكون لها نصيب؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Really?
هل حقا؟
Help out in the store for wages.
مساعدة في المتجر للأجور.
After all,
بعد كل شيء،
you just want me to do many chores.
أنت فقط تريد مني القيام بالعديد من الأعمال المنزلية.
Mother asked you to come, right?
طلبت منك الأم أن تأتي ، أليس كذلك؟
So what if I asked her to ask you?
فماذا لو طلبت منها أن تسألك؟
Mother,
الأم،
let Qingmu explain to you later.
دع Qingmu يشرح لك لاحقًا.
How dare you say that?
كيف تجرؤ على أن تقول ذلك؟
Qingmu has been influenced by you.
لقد تأثرت Qingmu بك.
My son and his wife are rich,
ابني وزوجته ثريان ،
but you never honour me, your mother.
لكنك لا تكرمني أبدًا يا أمك.
I'm just a joke now.
أنا مجرد مزحة الآن.
A joke in the entire village.
نكتة في القرية كلها.
Somebody in there?
شخص ما هناك؟
(Da Niu)
(دا نيو): شخص ما هناك؟
Da Niu?
نعم نيو؟
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
It's Dragon Boat Festival.
إنه مهرجان قوارب التنين.
I'm here to visit
أنا هنا لزيارة
my grandaunt.
حفيدي.
He's ill-intentioned.
إنه ذو نية سيئة.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
You must be Pang Longyue.
يجب أن تكون بانغ لونجيوي.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
When Li family was building the house,
عندما كانت عائلة لي تبني المنزل ،
my father contributed the most.
ساهم والدي أكثر.
Half of the house
نصف المنزل
should be mine.
يجب أن يكون لي.
It's fine if you don't want to share it.
لا بأس إذا كنت لا ترغب في مشاركته.
Give me money.
أعطني نقودا.
We have heavy debts.
لدينا ديون ثقيلة.
We have no money for you.
ليس لدينا مال لك.
I don't care!
لا أهتم!
I'll not go easy on you!
لن اكون سهل عليك!
- Mother! - Be careful!
- الأم!  - كن حذرا!
What?
ماذا؟
You've earned so much. Are you trying not to pay me?
لقد ربحت الكثير.  هل تحاول ألا تدفع لي؟
It has nothing to do with you whether we're earning money or not.
لا علاقة لك بما إذا كنا نكسب المال أم لا.
If you don't give me money today,
إذا لم تعطيني المال اليوم ،
I'll destroy your house.
سأدمر منزلك.
You just want money, right? I'll give you money.
أنت فقط تريد المال ، أليس كذلك؟  سأعطيك المال.
Don't be scared.
لا تخف.
Longyue.
لونجيوي.
That should be enough.
ينبغي أن يكون كافيا.
No, this is not enough.
لا ، هذا لا يكفي.
I didn't even collect rent from you all these years.
لم أقم حتى بتحصيل الإيجار منك كل هذه السنوات.
I'll come back next time.
سأعود في المرة القادمة.
Why are you so unreasonable?
لماذا أنت غير معقول إلى هذا الحد؟
Qingmu, he took our money.
Qingmu ، أخذ أموالنا.
Give it back or I'll beat you.
أعيدها أو سأضربك.
Don't beat me, Niu. I'm scared.
لا تهزمني ، نيو.  أنا خائف.
Here.
هنا.
Dear.
عزيزي.
Take this, too.
خذ هذا أيضًا.
You know your place.
أنت تعرف مكانك.
Qingmu.
تشينغمو.
Da Niu is greedy.
دا نيو جشع.
Giving him money won't solve the problem.
إعطائه المال لن يحل المشكلة.
Mother, I need to go out.
أمي ، أنا بحاجة إلى الخروج.
Where are you going?
إلى أين تذهب؟
Qingmu is really a coward.
Qingmu هو حقا جبان.
If my husband is still alive,
إذا كان زوجي لا يزال على قيد الحياة ،
we won't be bullied.
لن يتم تخويفنا.
You're a jinx!
أنت النحس!
You...
أنت...
Shut up!
اسكت!
If you ever scold Longyue again,
إذا كنت تأنيب لونجيوي مرة أخرى ،
I'll not go easy on you!
لن اكون سهل عليك!
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Come and rest for a while.
تعال واسترح لبعض الوقت.
Drink some tea.
شرب بعض الشاي.
Thank you, mother.
شكرا امي.
Did you hear that
هل سمعت هذا
the officers are here to arrest someone?
الضباط هنا لاعتقال شخص ما؟
Who?
من؟
Da Niu.
نعم نيو.
Da Niu?
نعم نيو؟
I heard that he was charged for blackmailing others
سمعت أنه متهم بابتزاز الآخرين
and he was arrested
واعتقل
with evidence.
مع الأدلة.
That's great.
ذلك رائع.
Qingmu is back.
عودة Qingmu.
Did you see how Da Niu was arrested?
هل رأيت كيف تم القبض على دا نيو؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
Don't say I didn't remind you.
لا تقل أنني لم أذكرك.
If you don't get the money,
إذا لم تحصل على المال ،
you'll be embarrassed.
سوف تشعر بالحرج.
I'll get Pang Longyue to give me the money.
سأجعل بانج لونجيوي يعطيني المال.
♪You're the fated love coming from the immortal world♪
أنت الحب المقدّر الآتي من العالم الخالد
♪You tie the red strings on the tips of my fingers♪
♪ تقوم بربط الخيوط الحمراء على أطراف أصابعي ♪
♪My heart won't change even if time passes♪
♪ قلبي لن يتغير حتى لو مر الوقت
♪I'll wait for the love in the old place as promised♪
♪ سأنتظر الحب في المكان القديم كما وعدت ♪